nvidia.in 2017-06-12

# NVIDIA Privacy Policy | NVIDIA

**This policy was last updated on June 15, 2016.**

NVIDIA is committed to respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to our world-wide family of NVIDIA-operated websites (including www.nvidia.com, www.slizone.com, 3DVision Live, GeForce.com, GTC, TegraZone.com, and shield.nvidia.com) and mobile apps and hardware and software products including any internet-connected devices (our “Services”).

#### 1\. Introduction

NVIDIA is committed to implementing appropriate protections for any Personal Information that we collect or our users share with us.

NVIDIA's Online Privacy Policy and Kids Privacy Policy set forth our policies and procedures regarding our collection, use, and/or sharing of your Personal Information.

Please note: The NVIDIA Online Store is managed independently by Digital River, Inc., and is subject exclusively to the Digital River Privacy Statement.

#### 2\. What Information We May Collect

When you use our Services, we may collect "Personal information," which is any information that can be used to identify a particular individual which can include traditional identifiers such as name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and non-traditional identifiers such as unique device identifiers and Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.

We may collect personal information that you or other users give us (e.g. your contact details or your comments or opinions), allow us to receive either through your preferences in your devices (e.g. location data) or browser or from third parties such as social networks (e.g. your public profile information) or through use of our Services (e.g. the pages you visit).

[CLICK HERE] to learn more about how Personal Information is collected.

We collect Personal Information about our users in several ways.

 **Personal Information You Provide to Us**

Most of the Personal Information we receive comes to us voluntarily from our users in the course of using our Services. For example, Personal Information may be collected when you:

  * Register or log in to our Services;
  * Participate in activities available through our Services such as a sweepstakes, contests, games and promotional offers;
  * Sign up for a newsletter;
  * Provide information to our customer service representatives or contact us through our Services;
  * Use our message boards and other public forums available through our Services;
  * Use any social networking features available through our Services and create a profile or share information about yourself;
  * Apply for employment or a position online.

**Personal Information Collected Via Technology**

As you use our Services, we may collect passive information through the use of cookies, web beacons, log file information and other tracking technologies, including your IP address, browser type, device type, device ID, geolocation data, Uniform Resource Locators (URL) and operating system 

We use this technology and identifiers to better understand how you interact with our Services. In particular, we gather information on the date and time you connect or engage with our Services, the products you reviewed, the areas of our Services you interact with any referring or destination pages or websites. 

This information allows us to better understand our users and to enhance your experience. For example, when you return to our website after visiting another site, cookies allow our website to remember who you are and any preferences you have. For more information on who we use cookies, please see our cookie policy. 

In addition, collecting information such as device type allows us to optimize settings for your system remotely.

**Personal Information We Receive From Others**

We may receive Personal Information about users from third parties such as web analytics vendors, social media sites, law enforcement agencies and marketing consultants.

This information supplements any information that we have collected directly from our users, and allows us to customize our Services to better serve you. Sometimes, we may receive Personal Information about people who are not yet users of our Services. NVIDIA's policy is to treat all information obtained from third parties in the same manner that we treat information that we have collected ourselves.

#### 3\. Why We Collect Personal Information

The Personal Information we collect helps us.

  * provide our Services to you;
  * process transactions; 
  * respond to requests or any correspondence you send us;
  * and learn about our users' interests in terms of the features, performance and support of our products;
  * customize your experience (including the content and advertisements delivered on our websites);
  * to enhance and develop our Services;
  * to protect and enforce our rights and the rights of our users and third parties;
  * market our products and services to you through newsletters or promotional e-mails or push notifications (Please see the section below on Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information.)

#### 4\. How We May Share Your Information 

We do not sell Personal Information about our customers or users to any third parties. We may from time to time share your Personal Information with our business partners, resellers, affiliates, service providers, consulting partners and others in order to provide our Services to you. 

[CLICK HERE]to learn more how we may share your Personal Information with our business partners and others. For further information on your choices regarding your information, see the “Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information” section below.

Any Personal Information we collect may be shared with NVIDIA's corporate affiliates, or companies who operate under the same corporate control. NVIDIA will take reasonable steps to ensure that these company affiliates honor this Online Privacy Policy and Kids Privacy Policy.

We may, from time to time, share your Personal Information with third party business partners, vendors, affiliates, and other service providers that perform services on our behalf, in order to carry out their work for us, which may include identifying and serving targeted advertisements, e-commerce, content or service fulfillment, website operations, email communications management, customer service, analytics, manufacturing, integration, delivery, support, payment, and servicing processes. NVIDIA's policy is to prohibit these companies from using your Personal Information for any purpose other than to provide the services expressly requested by NVIDIA.

We may with your prior consent share your Personal Information with business partners who offer a service jointly with us, for example, when running a co-sponsored contest or promotion, or offering a co-branded product or service.

NVIDIA may sell or buy assets from or to other companies. Personal information may be one of the transferred business assets, and would likely be one of the transferred assets in the event that NVIDIA or some of its assets were acquired. If NVIDIA or its assets are acquired by another company, NVIDIA will request that the acquiring company assumes the obligations of this Online Privacy Policy and Kids Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on NVIDIA; or (b) to protect and defend the rights or property of NVIDIA or users of our website.

NVIDIA may "de-personalize" Personal Information by removing personally identifiable characteristics, such as name and email address, and aggregate data for use in surveys or other business purposes. NVIDIA may then use and/or share this de-personalized information with third parties to improve our Services.

#### 5\. Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information

NVIDIA respects your choices about how your Personal Information is used when you register with us, elect to receive our newsletters, or provide us with Personal Information for other purposes.

If you choose not to provide any Personal Information when requested, you can still enjoy most aspects of our Services. However, you may be unable to access certain areas and services that require our interaction with you.

**Marketing communications**. You can opt-out of receiving communications from NVIDIA at any time by unsubscribing at <https://profile.nvidia.com/en-us/login>, or by following the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of any e-mail or SMS communications you receive. If you are using our apps we may also send you push notifications which you can opt out of receiving using the app settings. However, we may still send you updates to our Legal Notices, Online Privacy Policy, or regarding any account you have created with us.

**Online advertising and other tracking**. As discussed above, NVIDIA and our third-party partners collect certain information about you when you use our Services through technology such as cookies, web beacons and similar tracking tools for internal and analytic purposes. You may be able to "opt out" of the collection of information through cookies or other tracking technology by actively managing the settings on your browser or mobile device. Please refer to your browser's or mobile device's technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools. To learn more about cookies, please read our cookie policy at <http://www.nvidia.co.uk/object/cookie-policy-uk.html>. We are not able to respond to "Do Not Track" signals set by a browser at this time.

We also permit third party online advertising networks and social media companies to collect information about your use of our website over time so that they may play or display ads that may be relevant to your interests on our site as well as on other websites or apps. Typically, this information is collected through cookies or similar tracking technologies, which recognize the device you are using and collect information, including for example, hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date you visited the site, and other information. This information is used to display targeted ads on or through our Services, or to our users or visitors to our websites on other websites or apps, including on Facebook. We may combine personal information that we collect about you with the browsing and tracking information collected by these technologies. We or the online advertising networks use this information to make the advertisements you see online more relevant to your interests. For example, we use third party advertising services such as Remarketing with Google Analytics to market our services to you on other websites. You may be able to “opt out” of the collection of information through cookies or other tracking technology by actively managing the settings on your browser or mobile device. Please refer to your browser’s or mobile device’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools. (To learn more about cookies, clear gifs/web beacons and related technologies, and to learn how you may be able to opt-out of interest-based advertising from many online advertising networks, you may wish to visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/), the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices)). If you access our service on your mobile device, you may not be able to control tracking technologies through settings.

#### 6\. EU rights relating to Accessing and Correcting Personal Information

[CLICK HERE] to access NVIDIA's EU policy relating to Accessing and Correcting Personal Information.

You have the following rights in relation to your personal information: (i) the right to be informed about how your personal information is being used; (ii) the right to access the personal information we hold about you; and (iii) the right to request the correction of inaccurate personal data we hold about you and to request the blocking or deletion of your personal information where the processing does not comply with local data protection laws. To exercise any of the above rights, or if you have any questions relating to your rights, please contact us by using the details set out in the "Contact Us" section below.

#### 7\. Kids Privacy Policy

We take care to protect the privacy of children under the age of 13 who visit our websites or mobile apps.

[CLICK HERE] to access NVIDIA's **Kids Privacy Policy**. 

#### 8\. Links to Other Sites

We are not responsible for any content, products or services offered on any third-party websites. Links to third-party websites are provided for your convenience only. This Privacy Policy will not apply to any Personal Information that you provide to, or that is collected by, any third-party website operator or third-party product/service provider.

Additionally, our site may include social media features such as Facebook, Twitter and Pinterest buttons (such as “Like,” “Tweet” or “Pin”). These social media sites may automatically record information about your browsing behavior every time you visit a site that has a social media button, regardless of whether you click on the button. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the feature, not by our privacy policy. Please review your privacy settings on social media sites.

#### 9\. Security

We will take all reasonable and appropriate measures to protect the personal information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.

#### 10\. How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about NVIDIA's Online Privacy Policy or Kids Privacy Policy, please send an email to [privacy@nvidia.com](mailto:privacy@nvidia.com) or write to us at: NVIDIA Corporation, 2701 San Tomas Expressway, Santa Clara, CA 95050.

#### 11\. Notice To California Residents – Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83 (known as the "Shine the Light" law), NVIDIA customers who are residents of California may request certain information about our disclosure of personal information during the prior calendar year to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the following address:

**In the United States:**  
NVIDIA Corporation  
2701 San Tomas Expressway  
Santa Clara, CA 95050

Alternatively, you may send us an email at [CaliforniaPrivacyDisclosure@nvidia.com](mailto:CaliforniaPrivacyDisclosure@nvidia.com).

#### 12\. Online Privacy Policy Updates

We may make changes to our Online Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review our policies regularly as updated policies will apply to your future visits to our website.

#### 12\. Your Consent

By using this website, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to NVIDIA's collecting and processing of your Personal Information for the purposes listed herein. Your Personal Information may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in the United States and other countries in which NVIDIA's backup storage may be located.
